We are sitting here in what used to be Kfar Aza’s neighborhood for young families. What should happen to this place?
We don't know yet.
We are waiting for them,
we want them back,
not just them, there is another 46 people,
A part of them lives, the others, not.
We will not decide about this area
until they will be back.
I'll show you later on,
you can take a picture of trees,
a part of the new...
the neighborhood was already fixed,
there is part of it that is not fixed.
Because we have
a Jewish tradition that we are keeping a little bit
of the wall not finished,
until the Beit HaMikdash, the temple,
will be rebuilt again.
So we did it,
and we will fix it just after all the 48 people will be back.
And this neighborhood,
we will decide what to do with it,
just after Gali and Ziv will be back.
Talia is waiting,
Talia, the mother
and Doron and the two brothers.
I'm talking with them a lot and
they're waiting.
I don't know if you saw my wife,
my wife is a lot in the media.
She's a famous, not like me,
and always with a shirt of Gali and Ziv (Berman),
or Omri (Miran) from Nahal Oz,
our neighbors, or something else.
We are living around those 48 people,
we're doing everything
that no one will forget them over there.
This is our job now.